hi welcome to this screencast on the
嗨，欢迎来到
said garbage collector
说垃圾收集器
I'm patty diem I'm an engineer in the
我是小馅饼，我是工程师
Java platform group at Oracle working on
Oracle的Java平台小组致力于
garbage collection
垃圾收集
so I'll start by giving an overview of
因此，我将首先概述
what said UC is and how it works we'll
UC是什么以及它如何工作，我们将
have a look at some performance numbers
看看一些性能数字
and I'll end by showing you how to get
最后，我将向您展示如何获得
started using CGC
开始使用CGC
so said you see is a new garbage
所以说你看到是一个新的垃圾
collector which is available it has an
可用的收集器有一个
experimental feature in starting with
开始的实验功能
JDK 11 we described said you see as a
我们描述的JDK 11表示您认为
scalable low latency garbage collector
可扩展的低延迟垃圾收集器
and to get a little bit better
并变得更好一点
understanding of what we mean with that
了解我们的意思
let's have a look at the goals we have
让我们来看看我们的目标
in mind when designing this so when we
在设计时要牢记，所以当我们
say it's a low latency GC we mean that
说这是一个低延迟的GC，我们的意思是
GC post times never exceed 10
GC发布时间永远不会超过10
milliseconds and when we say it's
毫秒，当我们说这是
scalable we mean that this GC can handle
可扩展性是指该GC可以处理
heaps ranging from small to very large
从小到大的堆
where very large means multi terabytes
其中很大意味着数兆兆字节
here are some of the key features of
以下是一些主要功能
said you see at its core said you see is
说你看到的是核心
a concurrent garbage collector which
并发垃圾收集器
means that all the heavy lifting down by
意味着所有沉重的重担
a GC is done while your threads continue
当您的线程继续时，GC已完成
to execute so things like marking
执行这样的标记
compaction and all other expensive
压实和所有其他昂贵的
operations are handled without stopping
操作不停地处理
the Java threads said you see currently
Java线程说您当前看到
has a single generation under the hood
在引擎盖下只有一代
it uses load barriers and caller
它使用负载屏障和呼叫者
pointers as the main techniques to
指针作为主要技术
achieve concurrency its region based
实现基于区域的并发
which means that the heap is divided
这意味着堆被分割了
into many smaller regions and said you
进入许多较小的地区，并说你
see can choose to only compact a subset
看到可以选择只压缩一个子集
of those typically those that contain
在那些通常包含
the most garbage and it's also Numa wear
最垃圾，也是努玛的衣服
so when a job object or javathread
所以当一个作业对象或javathread
allocates an object that object will be
分配一个对象，该对象将是
allocated in memory that is local to the
分配给本地内存
CPU key prop
CPU钥匙道具
you've said you see is that post times
你说过你看到的是发布时间
do not increase with the heap size or
不随堆大小增加或
lives it size so it doesn't matter if
保持其大小，因此无论是否
you have a one gig heap or a one
你有一堆或一堆
terabyte II post times will not be
TB级的发布时间将不会
affected by that
受此影响
so let's have a quick look at what
让我们快速看一下
happens when said you see is collecting
当你说你正在收集时发生
garbage so this picture shows you what a
垃圾，这张照片告诉你什么
GC cycle looks like inside you see and
GC周期看起来像您看到的内部
the different places it goes through and
它经历的不同地方
blue arrows here pointing downwards
这里的蓝色箭头指向下方
represent these forces and gray arrows
代表这些力量和灰色箭头
pointing sideways represent concurrent
指向侧面表示并发
phases so let me walk you through a GC
阶段，让我引导您完成GC
cycle and briefly describe what's going
循环并简要描述正在发生的事情
on in each of these phases
在每个阶段中
so the cycle starts with the mark start
所以循环从标记开始
pause this is where thread stacks are
暂停，这是线程堆栈所在的位置
scan to find object pointers these
扫描以找到这些对象的指针
object pointers are also known as routes
对象指针也称为路由
we then continue with a concurrent mark
然后，我们继续并发标记
phase and this is where this is an
阶段，这是一个
expensive operation where the GC walks
GC运行的昂贵操作
entire object graph and marking the
整个对象图并标记
objects it finds as live we then come to
它发现的物体是真实的，然后我们来到
the mark and pause this is a
标记和暂停这是一个
synchronization point to coordinate the
同步点以协调
end of the marking phase and once this
标记阶段结束，一旦完成
has been reached the GC now has complete
已经到达GC现在已经完成
lioness information so it knows which
母狮信息，因此它知道哪个
objects are live and which are garbage
对象是活动的，是垃圾
and we now transition to the concurrent
现在我们过渡到并发
prepare for relocate phase
准备搬迁阶段
in this phase number of things happens
在这个阶段发生了很多事情
but I'll just highlight two of the more
但我只强调其中两个
interesting parts here which is
这里有趣的部分是
reference processing and relocation set
参考处理和重定位集
selection so reference processing is
选择，因此参考处理是
where the GC takes care of soft week and
GC负责软周的工作，
phantom references and finalization and
幻像引用和定稿以及
the relocation set selection is where
重定位集选择在哪里
the GC figures out what parts of the
GC会找出
heap needs to be compacted to free up
堆需要压缩以释放
memory we then transition to the
记忆，然后我们过渡到
relocation phase this starts with the
搬迁阶段始于
relocate start pause where thread stacks
在线程堆栈处重新定位开始暂停
are scanned to handle roots pointing
进行扫描以处理根源指向
into the location set and we then come
进入位置集，然后我们来
to the concurrent relocate face and this
到并发搬迁的面孔，这
is where the heavy work of compacting
是压实的繁重工作
the heap happens and by compacting the
堆发生并通过压缩
heap the GC will free up large
堆GC将释放大空间
contiguous chunks of memory and make
连续的内存块和
that memory available for new
该内存可用于新
allocations
分配
and that completes the Jesus icon I want
这样就完成了我想要的耶稣圣像
to point out here that the Jesus cycles
在这里指出耶稣循环
that we have here will be very short as
我们在这里会很短
I mentioned before the reason why I said
我之前提到我为什么说
you see can keep these forces below 10
你看可以将这些力量保持在10以下
milliseconds is because no heavy lifting
毫秒是因为没有沉重的负担
is done while the jaw threats are
在下颚威胁时完成
stopped all that is down here is
停止了这里所有的一切
essentially scanning or threat stacks
本质上是扫描或威胁堆栈
and this typically can be done well
这通常可以很好地完成
within the limits of 10 milliseconds
在10毫秒内
okay so let's have a look at some
好吧，让我们来看一些
performance numbers this shows you the
性能数字可以向您显示
score us from spectator be comparing
从观众那里给我们打分，进行比较
said you see with a parallel GC and g1
说你用并行GC和g1看到
spec jb b is a well-known java benchmark
spec jb b是著名的java基准
which produces two scores max j ups and
最多产生两个得分j ups和
critical j ups max yelps is a raw
关键jups max yelps是原始的
throughput score while critical j ups is
吞吐率得分，而关键因素是
a latency sensitive score showing the
潜伏期敏感分数显示
throughput achieved under an SLA and as
根据SLA和
we can see on this benchmark you said
我们可以在这个基准上看到你说的
you see is on par with a parallel GC and
您看到的与并行GC相当，并且
g1 when it comes to raw throughput and
原始吞吐量为g1
said you see is well ahead the hell of
说你看到了
the other collectors when it comes to
其他收藏家
the latency sensitive score and this is
延迟敏感分数，这是
of course thanks to the little cost
当然要感谢小成本
times here we have the GC post times for
在这里，我们有GC的发布时间
the same benchmark the light blue bars
基准相同的浅蓝色条
here show the average post time for each
这里显示每个的平均发布时间
GC and the black part shows the worst
GC和黑色部分显示最差
post time and then we have some of the
发布时间，然后我们有一些
higher percentiles in between the post
职位之间的百分比更高
times for cdc barely registers here so
cdc的时间几乎不在这里注册
to get a better sense of what's going on
更好地了解正在发生的事情
lets me switch the time axis to use a
让我切换时间轴以使用
logarithmic scale
对数刻度
like that and now we can see that the
这样，现在我们可以看到
average post time for CDC is roughly one
CDC的平均发布时间约为1
millisecond with the worst post time of
毫秒，最差的发布时间
around two milliseconds and this is well
大约两毫秒，这很好
below sadducees goal of never having
低于萨杜迪的目标
pauses exceeding 10 milliseconds in
暂停时间超过10毫秒
contrast we can see that the other
对比我们可以看到另一个
collectors have average post times
收藏家的平均发帖时间
between 150 and 200 milliseconds with
在150到200毫秒之间
the worst post times on the order of 300
最差的发布时间约为300
to 500 milliseconds
到500毫秒
you
您
let's have a look at what you need to
让我们来看看你需要
know to get started using said you see
知道开始使用说你明白
first of all there is a new JVM option
首先有一个新的JVM选项
to enable said you see and that's called
使说你看到，这叫做
you said you see since this is still an
您说您看到了，因为这仍然是
experimental feature you also need to
实验功能，您还需要
supply the option to unlock experimental
提供解锁实验性选项
features and a few words on tuning so
功能和关于调整的几句话
first of all we've been working hard to
首先我们一直在努力
make said you see easy to do and to
说你觉得容易做
avoid exposing a lot of GC tuning
避免暴露很多GC调整
options
选项
the main tuning option is setting the
主要的调整选项是设置
max heap size and since said UC is a
最大堆大小，并且由于所说的UC是一个
concurrent collector you need to select
您需要选择的并发收集器
a max heap size that well first of all
首先最大的最大堆大小
can accommodate the live set of your
可以容纳您的现场演出
application but you also need to have
应用程序，但您还需要
enough Headroom in the heap to allow
堆中有足够的净空以允许
allocations to be serviced
要分配的分配
while the G's is running how much
G跑了多少
Headroom you need very much depends on
您需要的净空高度取决于
the allocation rate and the live set
分配率和现场布置
size of your application and general the
您的应用程序大小和一般
more memory you give to said you see the
你给更多的记忆说你看到
better but at the same time you don't
更好，但同时您却没有
want to waste memory so it's all about
想浪费内存，所以一切都在这里
finding a balance between memory usage
在内存使用之间找到平衡
and how often the GC needs to run the
以及GC需要多久运行一次
second tuner option that you might want
您可能想要的第二个调谐器选项
to look at is setting the number of
要看的是设置
concurrent GC threads said UC has
并发GC线程表示UC具有
heuristics to select this number and
启发式选择此数字，然后
this usually works well but depending on
这通常效果很好，但是取决于
what type of workload you're running you
您正在运行哪种类型的工作负载
might want to adjust this this option
可能要调整此选项
basically it says how much CPU time
基本上说多少CPU时间
you're willing to give to the GC and if
你愿意给GC，如果
you give it too much then the GC will
你给它太多，那么GC会
steal too much CPU time from your
从您的服务器上窃取过多的CPU时间
application but on the other hand if
申请，但另一方面
this number is too low then the GC might
此数字太低，则GC可能
not be able to keep up and that's
无法跟上，那就是
basically it when it comes to tuning
基本上是调音
there are a few other options but these
还有其他一些选择，但是这些
are the two main options you want to
是您要选择的两个主要选项
look at when tuning set you see
看一下调音台
to enable logging I'd recommend you use
启用日志记录，我建议您使用
one of the following two options X log
以下两个选项之一X日志
GC will give you basic logging with a
GC将为您提供基本的日志记录
single line printed per GC this line
每行GC每行打印一行
will only provide high-level information
仅提供高级信息
such as why the GC was triggered and
例如触发GC的原因，以及
what the heap size or heap usage was
堆大小或堆使用量是多少
before and after the GC X log G C star
GC X log GC星号之前和之后
will give you a more detailed logging
将为您提供更详细的日志记录
this can be useful when tuning or if you
这在调优或如果您
just want more information on what's
只想了解更多信息
going on under the hood
引擎盖下继续
Sadducees currently only available on
Sadducees目前仅在
Linux x86 64 bit additional platforms
Linux x86 64位其他平台
might be supported in the future if
如果将来可能会支持
there is enough demand for them
对他们有足够的需求
so to summarize said UC offers low
综上所述，UC提供了低
latency with the post time staying below
延迟时间低于发布时间
10 milliseconds it's scalable so you can
10毫秒可扩展，因此您可以
have a huge heap without affecting the
有一大堆而不影响
GC pause times it's easy to tune and
GC暂停时间很容易调整和
it's available in JDK 11 you can find
您可以在JDK 11中找到它
additional information on that you see
您看到的其他信息
on the open JDK wiki
在开放的JDK Wiki上
download JDK 11 today at Oracle comm /
立即从Oracle comm下载JDK 11 /
Java download and if you're interested
Java下载，如果您有兴趣
in participating in open JDK development
参与开放的JDK开发
go to open JDK java.net or you can
打开JDK java.net或可以
follow us on Twitter for news and
在Twitter上关注我们以获取新闻和
updates thanks for watching
更新感谢您的观看
[Music]
[音乐]